I'm not going to make a long introduction to this next individual we all know him
as a true modern day hero
going against the tide, not afraid, fearless
and we are so grateful that he's agreed to join us
Robert F. Kennedy Jr.
[applause]
Thank you everybody
I want to thank all of you stalwarts for coming here and I want to thank particularly
Ron Paul for hosting you, for keeping the flame alive, for his
life-long commitment to civil rights, to the bill of rights
and to the Constitution. There are many many areas and differences in our political opinions over the past
40 years that both of us have been in politics
both of us share a reverence for the bill of rights, and I think ultimately it's the retreat
fortress where all of us are holding up today
Excuse my voice which usually gets better as I talk
I wanna talk about the thing that we have in common which is the erosion of the Constitution
I gave a speech in Berlin I think last August
In the beginning of the pandemic, where I talked about
Hermann Göring's observition at Nuremberg
where he was on trial and eventually executed
He said at that time, he didn't say in Nuremberg transcripts
He said in a private conversation with a psychologist
called Gustave Gilbert who was given access to the prisioners in Nuremberg
And that discrepancy by the way has been exploited by the modern
propaganda juggernaut, "fact-checking" organizations which of course are funded
by Bill Gates, by Facebook, by the medical cartel, by the State Department
saying that he never said these words at Nuremberg,
and it's true he didn't said them in the transcript of Nuremberg
but they were recorded by Gustave Gilbert
and what he said is, Gilbert said to him:
How did you do this to the German people?
And he started explaining all their propaganda techniques
and Gilbert interrupted him and said: "that couldn't happen in a democracy
because there's free choice, there's critical thinking" and he said
"You can do this", Goring said
"You can do this in any system"
"It doesn't matter if it's a democracy, monarchy or a communist system"
"or a fascist system"
"All you need to do is invoke fear"
"You tell the people they're under attack"
"that you're the only one who can save them"
"and anybody who disagrees with you is a threat to the commonwealth"
"They will do anything that you tell them to do"
And today, you know, Hitler was democratically elected
by the most well-educated people in the planet, a highest level of education
and some of the most tolerant people in Europe at that time
the reason there were so many Jews in Germany
is because they fled. Germany was very bad to the Jews long before Hitler
but much less bad than the eastern-european countries
or Spain or the other countries from which they fled to come to Germany
So you had a people that historically were tolerant
open-minded, questioning and critical
and probably the Weimar republic was the strongest democracy in Europe
and Hitler was elected, he did not take over
he was elected by people
who he was able... He had 3% of the vote in the previous election
and then he won with a majority
because he was able to manipulate the use of fear
And we've seen one of the alarming parts of this pandemic
for those of us who were a little conversant
with the kind of medical paradigms that are being invoked right now
to understand with such clarity
manipulations that are taking place, the chicanery
hiding of real data
the obscuring of all these true facts and figures that we could
use to make rational policy decisions
how did case fatality rates
likened to the seasonal flu for each age group?
who is dying at what age, who is not?
what are the real death counts from covid?
CDC has admitted that 96%
of the people... Only 4% of the people who it classifies
as having died from covid died from only covid
and the average of potentially fatal comorbidities in the remaining 96% is 3.8
the people who died, 96% of them had
almost 4 other reasons that might have killed them
and the manipulation of the death certificates,
manipulation of the PCR test
all of these manipulations that are all designed
the Gates funded projection
from London and from IHME from Washington
which they used to manipulate the lockdowns
which we now see were 40 times the death rate
that actually was imposed by covid, so
all of these mechanisms appear to have been
deliberately manipulated to put our population in a state of fear
and what happens when you have a population in fear
you've the complete obliteration of critical thinking
and people stop asking questions, it's a biological impulse
we retreat to the hard-wired impulses
that were hard-wired into us during the 20.000 generations of the human race
was wondering the African savannas, small tribal groups
at war, embattled, besieged all the time, and the only way of survival
was to follow a strong male leader
to embrace a common orthodoxy that would provide unit cohesion
and then to practice blind obedience to the leader
and that's where we all go
in times of fear, unless we have something else
that says to us "I'm gonna question this"
"I'm gonna start questioning these things"
And when you start doing that with orthodoxies
now the official orthodoxies, the whole thing falls apart
but we have all seen this kind of bewildering imposition
of totalitarian controls in our society, attacks
on the United States constitution that are unprecedented in the American history
Remember during Civil War
Abraham Lincoln tried to abandon habeas corpus just one
provision of the United States constitution, the courts said "you can't do that"
there is no emergency exemption in the United States constitution
and there's certainly no pandemic exemption
and it's not that our frames didn't know about pandemics
there was a pandemic during the Revolutionary War
of smallpox, that brought the army of New England to a standstill for 3 months
and the all knew about it. There was another pandemic during the
American Revolution of malaria and Washington, ironically
used bark of the cinchona tree, which the modern analog is hydroxychloroquine, to end that pandemic
and so they knew what pandemics were, but they didn't put it in the United States constitution
that all of these rights will be suspended as soon as we have a pandemic
and James Madison said:
"the reason we put the right to free speech in the first ammendment,
is because all of the other civil rights, human rights, constitutional rights
are based upon it"
If a government can hide what he's doing by censoring its opponents
and silencing dissidents
it has license to do anything that it wants
so they got rid
they conspired with the social media
and the media, we now know, we have the emails that show
Fauci corresponding with Zuckerberg
telling him what to shut down and what not to shut down
and they shut down
the critics and once they did that
once they imposed censorship
and they close the debate off from public square
they were able to go after all the other ammendments
so went after religious freedoms
they closed the churches
in this country, every church in this country for a year
and they kept the liquor stores open as essential businesses
there's no protection of liquor stores in the United States constitution
there is protection of churches
and they abolished religious exemptions
they got rid of jury trials, one of the first things that they did
the 7th amendment right to jury trials, the 7th amendment says:
"under no conditions
will Americans be denied their right
to a trial by their peers in maters exceeding 25 dollars in value"
and anybody who claims, any corporation
that claims to be implementing a counter-measure is now immune from lawsuits
no matter if it's a vaccine maker, remdesivir maker
no matter how negligent that company is
no matter how reckless
grievous your injury or death
you cannot sue them
and that again is novel in American history
all these companies now, and I saw it yesterday
in the Theranos lawsuit
that the judge has banned unvaccinated jurors
and that ultimately we all know is now a political
implication, because you're getting rid of all the black jurors
a highest... 70% of blacks are unvaccinated
and you're getting rid of any juror
who knows how to do critical thinking
[applause]
they got rid of the rights of association
rights of assembly
by telling us we have to social distance from each other, we can't gather in crowds
imagine this
They got rid of property rights
they closed every business, a milion businesses in this country
without due process and without just compensation
in direct violation of the constitution
They got rid of
due process, notice and rule-making, we know how we pass rules in this country
In a democracy,
congress can pass rules
They can vote, they can deliberate as they see fit. A regulatory agency cannot do that
And the executive cannot do that
because the courts, and we all are freightened to death we're creating these unelected officials
We have to have some democratic control, you know
And I've been suing people for 40 years, governments, the EPA, the Interior Department
all the state EPAs
for doing kind of regulatory favors for industry without going through the regulatory process
Here's what you have to do when you pass a regulation, you have to propose a rule, you have to publish a proposed rule
Here's what we're gonna do, we're gonna get everybody to put on a mask
you have to publish an environmental impact statement
a regulatory impact statement and an economic impact statement saying
here's the science we used to support that rule
here's the justification for it
here's the people who we heard
and the financial cost to those people, and other cost
here are the group... here are the advantages and the benefits of that rule. It all has to be quantified
and then they have to give the public a chance to comment, notice and comment
the public then writes in and says "wait a minute"
"I run a wilderness kayaking group"
"that you're gonna put out of business and destroy"
"and there's no reason masks... there's no science saying masks
"will in these outside settings going to help"
"will you examine my business?"
every business have a right to write in and say we can do this we can do that we can mitigate the risk
so let's change the rule to accommodate that, so it's as narrowly tailored as possible, as the law requires
one of that happened
Then you have a public hearing
where Tony Fauci brings in all of his science
that say masks work... None
And all of his scientists he relied on, and he's not going to be able to find one
because we'll destroy them in depositions, and embarrass and humiliate them.
[applause]
And then we get to cross-examine them and they are cross-examining ours and then
and the administrative law judge
rewrites the rules and quotes "they aren't arbitrary and capricious" and then recommends them
and if they don't reflect the evidence we can sue the agency
so there's all of these democratic protections
all of that was waived
all of these things were imposed on us by fiat
with no discussion, no science cited
and, you know, also all of this track-and-trace
surveillance is violating our right to not have warrant-less searches and seizures
you go through the entire Bill of Rights
and with one exception, the 2nd amendment, they have all been obliterated
and the weird thing to me
is I grew up in a liberal milieu
where everybody I knew was saying
"the one thing we gotta do is protect the constitution"
and to have my side
as the ones who are advocating censorship
and these kind of controls and erosion and subversion of our
traditional Bill of Rights it's really...
it is surreal
We all read Kafka when growing up, we all read Orwell
we all watched... We read all the Robert Heinlein
all of these stories, these parables
about the imposition of totalitarianism, and none of us...
all of us knew what right was from wrong
and it's bizarre to me to see how people have forgotten those things
One of the things that... I'm writing this book now I'm about to publish this book
on Anthony Fauci, and
part of my journey writing that book --- it's taken me over an year of really intense research, was...
it took me into a kind of a journey to try to explain
how this could have happened in America
and one of the things that I discovered during this process
is that this, what's happening now, this lockstep
imposition of totalitarian controls, not just in America
but in every one of the liberal democracies in the world, and all of the other countries in the world
you know, China moved into Hong Kong and banned the last
democratic newspaper. Everywhere in the world we see these
we see liberal democracies and constitutional rights disappearing
and it all happened at once, as if it was planned
and I don't consider myself a conspiracy theorist
and it's though to imagine how anybody could have planned this, but then I stumbled on
these simulations, many of you saw the simulation
that took place in 201, Event 201
in October of 2019, so
we now know the virus started circulating around September 14th
so this took place when the virus was already circulating in Wuhan
and the people who took part in that
simulation were the deputy director of the CIA, Avril Haines, who's now
the number one person in control of the National Security Agency under Biden
and Bill Gates, of course, who financed it
people from the social media
groups, people from the biggest pharmaceutical companies, Johnson & Johnson
people from global corporate PR agencies
and health officials from all over the world, including a Chinese
and what were they simulating? they were simulating a pandemic
but they weren't simulating a medical response to that pandemic
they were simulating a militarized response
how do you use that pandemic
to, particularly in Event 201
to impose censorship globally
and that's what they were modelling. And look, particularly in episode 4
it's all about... and oddly, their preoccupation was
"how do we stop people from stop talking about the fact"
"that this virus may have been lab generated and released?"
so they're talking about that in October 2019 and I'm not making this up
you can go to the simulation and see this
"how do we shut these people up?". George Gao, the head of the
Chinese CDC is saying "we need to stop people from talking about that issue"
but as I looked at that issue I found there was another one called SPARS where they did the same thing
they're not talking about how do you quarantine the sick and care for them
instead they're "how do you lock down the healthy", something that's never been done in history
"how do you force people to wear masks? how do you force people to comply with forced isolation?"
"how do you bring in the military, how do you silence all dissent?"
They weren't talking about how do you get people to take vitamin D, and how do you build your immune system, and tell them
to lose weight, to exercise --- 80% of the people who died were overweight
and it was probably a lot more than that because they were counting people who died from lightning strikes and car crashes
and how do you develop therapeutic drugs, off-the-shelf therapeutic drugs
most obvious thing to do
to create a communication system among the world's 11 million doctors, people on the front-line treating the disease
so that every successful treatment protocol is called in, other people are given the opportunity
to repeat it
and then ways to assess which ones are working and which ones aren't and do really rapid
placebo control trials in hospitals all over the world
and to create field clinics where you're treating people who are not sick but are infected
and never have to go to the hospital
and develop protocols so they never have to leave their homes
you want to avoid hospitalizations
one because that's the reason they gave to shut down society
two if you can treat somebody before they leave their home
every time somebody leaves their home who is sick, and go into the hospital really sick
that is a super-spreader event
that person is spreading the disease to Uber drivers, to doctors, to nurses, to family members, to people on the street
you wanna treat them at home
give them the things we know kill viral replication
zinc and anything that enhances zinc like hydroxychloroquine, ivermectin and
a hundred other remedies that we now know
dramatically reduce the spread of this disease. And what was our protocol?
Our protocol was to do none of that. No treatment until you go to the hospital
Then your treatment are two things that are bound to kill you:
ventilators and remdesivir
And Tony Fauci knew that remdesivir would kill you
He knew that because in 2019 he tried to use it for Ebola, 2019
He tried to use it for Ebola and within
5 days of treatment it gave lethal side-effect to 54% of the people. The safety monitoring board
ordered him to terminate the use of that drug
He threw a phony, contrived
absolute fraudulent study that he manipulated and orchestrated of that drug
made it standard of care. It is homicide
And if you look, how does it kill people? Two ways... Three ways
kidney failure, heart failure and all-organ collapse
and what happened to the people who died in the pandemic, what were they dying of? Kidney failure
All the doctors said, you heard it again and again: we've never seen a virus that attacks the kidneys
Because it wasn't the virus. It was the Remdesivir
and he denied them deliberately, purposefully
access to the things that we know work because 248 studies show they do
which is Ivermecting and hydroxychloroquine. And all the others, even monoclonal
steroids antibodies which they know work, they denied to all the people in the nursing home when they could've given it to them
so, something about this smelled
it was suspecious and weird from the beginning. What I found during the course of my research
is that those simulations were not just confined to Event 201 and to SPARS
I found out over a dozen of them
and they did at least once every two years beginning in 2000
most of them were top secret
but they involved hundreds of thousands of people
They were doing these simulation with
all of the police forces, many of the big city police forces in our contry
with front-line doctors and nurses
with medical officials, with the big corporate officials, from the energy industry, from the medical cartels, from the pharmaceutical industry
And they were involving not just the United States
Canada, Mexico and all of the nations of Europe were all participating, secretly
and drilling this again, again and again
if you look at
the techniques that they were using, here's something that they have in common
virtually every one of those simulations involved
representatives from the CIA
and the scripts for them were written by people associated with the intelligence agencies
almost all of them had a well-known
American or European leader
heads of Denmark, Sweden, Sam Nunn,
Madeleine Albright, Gary Hart, would be at the head of them
and that gave them kind of an imprimatur of gravitas and legitimacy
all of these front-line workers were being asked to do weird things, not cure patients
but censor people. They all now have in their head
"this is what you do in a pandemic. This is a legitimate"
"way to respond to a pandemic. This is the only way to respond"
It's not to make people better, it's not to treat their illnesses
it's not to keep them alive, it's the clamp down to totalitarian controls
I wrote a book about my family's 60 year battle with the CIA
called American Values, and researching that
I went out and purchased, at great cost, some of them cost me thousads of dollars
the CIA manuals for
manipulating large populations, and
they wrote a series of manuals for the techniques that are useful
when the intelligence agencies want to go into...
or other foreign policy panjandrums,
wanna go into an indigenous society
to destroy local businesses
to isolate and destroy institutional structures
to destroy social structures and social relationships
to obliterate the economy, to create chaos
that will then create enough people in the country who will allow
a foreign entity to come in and clamp down centralized control
and almost all of the techniques that are outlined in those manuals
are the same techniques that they were practicing in these simulations
year after year after year with hundreds of thousands of people
and for example in the CIA manual, the CIA conducted
these well-known
programs called by various name, operation ARTICHOKE, MK-ULTRA, etc
in the late 50s, 60s and 70s
to develop ways of manipulating human beings on an individual basis and on a mass basis
and the most potent technique, incidentally, that they learned again, again and again, more potent than physical torture
was isolation. If you can isolate people, and they did this
with sensory deprivation tanks, but also locking people in solitary confinement
you can get them to do almost anything you want them after a certain period of time. It will drive them mad
because we're social animals, we're social beings
and when you tear this social fabric it makes people desperate, fearful
and obedient to do anything. Another technique is called Stockholm syndrome
which is a way of putting individuals
or large parts of humanity in lockdown, for long periods of time
and it induces a kind of mass psychosis
makes them grateful to their captors, makes them empathize with their captors
renders them obedient, believing that obedience
is the only path to salvation, absolute obedience
and it obliterates, again, critical thinking
but during this period, the CIA was funding